[Music]
[音乐]
这张情人节卡是关于如何
this Valentine card is about how to
真的要让妈妈的心高
这是一个没有心的例子
this Valentine card is about how to
raise a heart really high mother page so
展示整个东西如何折叠
高高举起一点
raise a heart really high mother page so
here's an example without the heart just
这里的例子，你的想法是一样的
打开页面，它只是解除
here's an example without the heart just
showing how the whole thing folds down
都是基于真正的机制
在这方面表达得非常好
showing how the whole thing folds down
and lifts up high there's another little
菲利普（Philippe）的书看起来像是大爆炸
颜色真的很棒
and lifts up high there's another little
example here it's the same idea that you
预订弹出窗口实际上相当容易
大多数时候，但我刚读的书
example here it's the same idea that you
open the page and it just lifts that
认为这本书真的很美
是你打开时要去的那个
open the page and it just lifts that
it's all based on a really mechanism
该页面，它上升到很高
页面，因此您需要测量
it's all based on a really mechanism
that's expressed really well in this
这是基于锐角V
我只看一看这就是
that's expressed really well in this
book by Philippe look big bang pop and
锐角V折
主要提升，然后这一点在这里
book by Philippe look big bang pop and
the colors are really fantastic in this
是不对称的平行折叠
教程6我已经测量了一些
the colors are really fantastic in this
book the pop-up is actually fairly easy
这个例子是V的基数
贴在这里的角度是67
book the pop-up is actually fairly easy
most of the time but the book I just
度，我测量了双方，所以
我就可以坚持下去
most of the time but the book I just
think the book is really beautiful this
下来，然后如果你看这些
这里有一块推高了
think the book is really beautiful this
is the one we're going for when you open
向上举起的手臂是
坚持这条线2,8
is the one we're going for when you open
the page and it rises really high above
后面的厘米
然后这是实际的部分
the page and it rises really high above
the page so you do need to measure in
这是每个V型折叠77度
这个高度是十点五
the page so you do need to measure in
this it's based on the acute angle V
厘米，然后手臂在哪里
将是将坚持的手臂
this it's based on the acute angle V
I'll just look at this one this is the
手臂粘在上肢上
在折痕上方1,5厘米处
I'll just look at this one this is the
acute angle V fold the that's doing the
手臂本身需要一些压力，所以
它必须是我得分的两倍
acute angle V fold the that's doing the
main lifting and then this bit here this
它在中间有一个选项卡
两端之间的距离
main lifting and then this bit here this
is the asymmetric parallel fold which is
制表符是十一点八厘米
所以我要胶合在一个
is the asymmetric parallel fold which is
tutorial 6 I've measured up some an
分钟，以便您了解
当您在这里查看地图时，
tutorial 6 I've measured up some an
example here this is the base the V is
尺寸长度是
你看着它向下折叠
example here this is the base the V is
going to stick down here the angle is 67
不对称，您实际上是从
这里你有长度
going to stick down here the angle is 67
degrees and I measured both sides so
推高地带加小块
最上面的是这十一点
degrees and I measured both sides so
I'll be able to just stick it straight
八加一五给你
十三点三和另一点
I'll be able to just stick it straight
down and then if you look at these they
在这个基础上，你有两个八分
在立柱上你得了十分
down and then if you look at these they
have a piece here that's pushing up the
五，所以你把那些加在一起
得到了十三点三，那是
have a piece here that's pushing up the
the arm that lifts right up this is
给你平衡这是一个平衡
不对称平行折叠我只是认为
the arm that lifts right up this is
going to stick to this line 2,8
一起确保它确实
实际工作，这将是我
going to stick to this line 2,8
centimeters behind the
会以这种方式坚持下去
我测量过的所有这些尺寸
centimeters behind the
and then this is the actual piece itself
我可以将胶水同时放在两面
时间
and then this is the actual piece itself
this is the v-fold 77 degrees on each
像往常一样一直粘到折痕
而不是一块的边缘
this is the v-fold 77 degrees on each
side this height is ten point five
卡胶下来，然后我们就
关闭它以确保它可以正常工作
side this height is ten point five
centimeters and then where the arm this
当你有一个双厚度条
这是两倍的厚度，因为它确实
centimeters and then where the arm this
will be the arm that will stick behind
承受一些压力，所以我坚持了
那里所有的测量
will be the arm that will stick behind
it the arm sticks onto this upper limb
隐藏在v折后面
这是十一点八
it the arm sticks onto this upper limb
1,5 centimeters above the crease and the
两个折痕之间厘米
我要用胶水将其折叠起来
1,5 centimeters above the crease and the
arm itself this takes some pressure so
所以你不会再看到所有
条或推条剥离双
arm itself this takes some pressure so
it has to be double thickness I scored
厚度使其具有额外的强度
总是很好地粘合它们，如果
it has to be double thickness I scored
it down the middle it's got a tab on
他们有折痕，这也使
更强大的是，我们去了那里
it down the middle it's got a tab on
each end the distance between the two
那么这将失去对这个指导方针
我要在页面上绘制的
each end the distance between the two
tabs is eleven point eight centimeters
首先将其粘贴到此最高位
我还没有标记这条线的距离
tabs is eleven point eight centimeters
so I'm going to glue that shut in a
它实际上是粘着的，但是很幸运
应该都很好地工作，所以把
so I'm going to glue that shut in a
minute and just so you understand the
那里的胶粘到那个
线
minute and just so you understand the
maps in this as you look at it here's
顺便说一句，一切都是平行的
V形折痕在此处
maps in this as you look at it here's
the dimensions the lengths this is if
与这条线相同的角度
用这只手臂将要抬起
the dimensions the lengths this is if
you look at it as it folds down it's
与中央折痕处于同一角度
作为这个，然后胶合
you look at it as it folds down it's
asymmetric you're actually working from
也平行所以所有这些折痕
他们现在都是平行的
asymmetric you're actually working from
here you've got the length of the
当它下来
这应该像我一样坚持
here you've got the length of the
pushing up strip plus the little piece
在那边放胶水
衬衫，这会像那样下去
pushing up strip plus the little piece
on the top that is this eleven point
这是平仓，您知道我们
可以打开它，看看它如何工作
on the top that is this eleven point
eight plus one point five that gives you
我们去那里实际上这似乎额外
我做的那块不是很结实
eight plus one point five that gives you
thirteen point three and the other bit
足够使它实际上屈曲
理想情况下，我可能会做到这一点
thirteen point three and the other bit
on the base you've got two point eight
三个或四个三个或四个厚度
然后我们可以理想地坚持我
on the base you've got two point eight
and on the upright you've got ten point
认为它会更厚
卡本来会更硬
and on the upright you've got ten point
five so you add those together you've
这一点更强大，这是基本的
想法，当您关闭它时，它就会折叠起来
five so you add those together you've
got thirteen point three so that's
所以不，我们的天空很高
卡，这是一个较小的示例，
got thirteen point three so that's
giving you balance this is a balanced
因为它更小而不是
卡片不是那么僵硬
giving you balance this is a balanced
asymmetric parallel fold I just think it
它确实站起来，似乎确实
实际工作比
asymmetric parallel fold I just think it
all together make sure that it does
我刚做的一个，也许我们可以
只是把这颗心从这里粘下来
all together make sure that it does
actually work this is going to go I'm
它到这一个那里是高高的天空
情人节卡
actually work this is going to go I'm
going to stick it on this way round so
[音乐]
[掌声]
going to stick it on this way round so
all these dimensions as I've measured it
您
[音乐]
all these dimensions as I've measured it
I can put glue on both sides at the same